{
  "facts" : {
    "24" : {
      "answer" : " this is an a",
      "question" : "this is a q"
    },
    "00556c13db983b8712a2d17af5f327e2" : {
      "answer" : "",
      "id" : "00556c13db983b8712a2d17af5f327e2",
      "question" : "How to Install Grub on Ubuntu"
    },
    "0a01ba8c2b00e1e1ef3daea3580d351f" : {
      "answer" : "new fact",
      "id" : "0a01ba8c2b00e1e1ef3daea3580d351f",
      "question" : "new fact homie",
      "trees" : {
        "bba74ab62a49c87f65ff7c429f63ff92" : true
      }
    },
    "0ae7c3ee894a117fe8f7f6dc2791c2aa" : {
      "answer" : "1960",
      "id" : "0ae7c3ee894a117fe8f7f6dc2791c2aa",
      "question" : "980+980",
      "trees" : {
        "780df048605c9bf27ae84d859cc1fdeb" : true
      }
    },
    "0c7cc3c289412889547f299ee0707a02" : {
      "answer" : "50",
      "id" : "0c7cc3c289412889547f299ee0707a02",
      "question" : "25+25",
      "trees" : {
        "9dfb611221913a0393641eabd695af16" : true
      }
    },
    "126b28d1a4184e4d7d99656feebd823b" : {
      "answer" : "If you have an HTML element with a CSS `display` value of `flex` and `flex-direction` value ",
      "id" : "126b28d1a4184e4d7d99656feebd823b",
      "question" : "What does flex-direction do?"
    },
    "162307c8c731a2d855cc7e5d2d2ed5d8" : {
      "answer" : "yup",
      "id" : "162307c8c731a2d855cc7e5d2d2ed5d8",
      "question" : "indeed more facts",
      "trees" : {
        "487f469c1ebb407cc4e9e378409c03ad" : true
      }
    },
    "176e7c8614ed6f917726512d6b143ba8" : {
      "answer" : "7",
      "id" : "176e7c8614ed6f917726512d6b143ba8",
      "question" : "2+5",
      "trees" : {
        "1af7791811001da5c00edc0dc2231956" : true
      }
    },
    "18defe22db29eeae626aef41e508c554" : {
      "answer" : "barack",
      "id" : "18defe22db29eeae626aef41e508c554",
      "question" : "what is obamas first name",
      "trees" : {
        "e0520a90d85851d5d499de653d92d887" : true
      }
    },
    "1b15cf9a10eb0bec7262316d2bec6641" : {
      "answer" : "this is a new fact",
      "id" : "1b15cf9a10eb0bec7262316d2bec6641",
      "question" : "this is a new fact",
      "trees" : {
        "1b4b4a8d797aa40d2b7d903cdbd8c3a9" : true
      }
    },
    "1d1ec14bc8010cbfb42ce160744248ff" : {
      "answer" : "3",
      "id" : "1d1ec14bc8010cbfb42ce160744248ff",
      "question" : "what is 2+1"
    },
    "1d8c1d64bb06bb7046a238cd1b2bcfb3" : {
      "answer" : "another new fat",
      "id" : "1d8c1d64bb06bb7046a238cd1b2bcfb3",
      "question" : "yet anothre new fact",
      "trees" : {
        "e5fe90c3606cbd0329d26e0f03c69812" : true
      }
    },
    "2001ff83e953eb8f32b4808a6f160330" : {
      "answer" : "809",
      "id" : "2001ff83e953eb8f32b4808a6f160330",
      "question" : "808",
      "trees" : {
        "ae11a0d7c09f5cb26a6f47be68978541" : true
      }
    },
    "203f889239f025ab24d21adf750e21c7" : {
      "answer" : "new a",
      "id" : "203f889239f025ab24d21adf750e21c7",
      "question" : "new q ",
      "trees" : {
        "73ecf1917157fca001644715d88ae92c" : true
      }
    },
    "263cc854bb71a48316f109069fbaba7f" : {
      "answer" : "1",
      "id" : "263cc854bb71a48316f109069fbaba7f",
      "question" : "1"
    },
    "26707356df8b624c8beab67ce5236121" : {
      "answer" : "404",
      "id" : "26707356df8b624c8beab67ce5236121",
      "question" : "202",
      "trees" : {
        "77897c715507a5b98d5f299d9965a240" : true
      }
    },
    "275e3aa86ad9b2f8154144be83507fb9" : {
      "answer" : "12",
      "id" : "275e3aa86ad9b2f8154144be83507fb9",
      "question" : "5+7"
    },
    "2b70754fee385ef9eca7b02c9a8bbfd9" : {
      "answer" : "196",
      "id" : "2b70754fee385ef9eca7b02c9a8bbfd9",
      "question" : "98+98",
      "trees" : {
        "ee9c8ef91bfac286cc285be1b2d608db" : true
      }
    },
    "2f25f6033a03b0c0ae1b72eae8ca1b2b" : {
      "answer" : "2500",
      "id" : "2f25f6033a03b0c0ae1b72eae8ca1b2b",
      "question" : "25",
      "trees" : {
        "ec6f6775a4f43ccea568f6d26a79deba" : true
      }
    },
    "2f2cd95f056dbaa163fe851a72de2645" : {
      "answer" : "yup",
      "id" : "2f2cd95f056dbaa163fe851a72de2645",
      "question" : "yup",
      "trees" : {
        "69b8c8170d591d5721f5c3e1911963a1" : true
      }
    },
    "341efa4830f32ad18815184b32b95117" : {
      "answer" : "orangecake",
      "id" : "341efa4830f32ad18815184b32b95117",
      "question" : "apple",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "34bd2fe8d329d9bc7b6c5e78397d1a1f" : {
      "answer" : "4",
      "id" : "34bd2fe8d329d9bc7b6c5e78397d1a1f",
      "question" : "what is 2+2"
    },
    "38d57a8ab1b91d3a3eb40eea46a2fa98" : {
      "answer" : "baquery1",
      "id" : "38d57a8ab1b91d3a3eb40eea46a2fa98",
      "question" : "al"
    },
    "38f650703cd33788d4eb2bc46d5547ec" : {
      "answer" : "65",
      "id" : "38f650703cd33788d4eb2bc46d5547ec",
      "question" : "5"
    },
    "425d5d47a48243fd8819b8eff868feb5" : {
      "answer" : "baquerque",
      "id" : "425d5d47a48243fd8819b8eff868feb5",
      "question" : "al"
    },
    "438f6786355b28ea1887335fbde42750" : {
      "answer" : "400",
      "id" : "438f6786355b28ea1887335fbde42750",
      "question" : "200+200",
      "trees" : {
        "4b1878f15a03498637f6fa85aed40d7a" : true
      }
    },
    "49d251c2e54959b0611038939c4e054e" : {
      "answer" : "one333-9999941414",
      "id" : "49d251c2e54959b0611038939c4e054e",
      "question" : "another one225---9994141414",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "4a245a3a3d7be71a592076ef2d2bc15f" : {
      "answer" : "31",
      "id" : "4a245a3a3d7be71a592076ef2d2bc15f",
      "question" : "11+20",
      "trees" : {
        "7b573980fad3a926150c87660707c26f" : true
      }
    },
    "4b4b4c2dbc0d6b7eb1d2892d01cbacb2" : {
      "answer" : "orange",
      "id" : "4b4b4c2dbc0d6b7eb1d2892d01cbacb2",
      "question" : "apple",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "4d31e5274647317d452a124745e1123b" : {
      "answer" : "198",
      "id" : "4d31e5274647317d452a124745e1123b",
      "question" : "99+99"
    },
    "4f5430fb0fd39072b50ff0b80c453dc3" : {
      "answer" : "hello",
      "id" : "4f5430fb0fd39072b50ff0b80c453dc3",
      "question" : ""
    },
    "4f9e03a824d42cbc77733f9c5ad83151" : {
      "answer" : "5",
      "id" : "4f9e03a824d42cbc77733f9c5ad83151",
      "question" : "5"
    },
    "514bce83764babe8ad1a6775deaf7658" : {
      "answer" : "140",
      "id" : "514bce83764babe8ad1a6775deaf7658",
      "question" : "70+70",
      "trees" : {
        "967fd26e6fb4280f892e29bbd9d320cf" : true
      }
    },
    "52128d0cb3c7d9afb91baed93f2a026e" : {
      "answer" : "yup",
      "id" : "52128d0cb3c7d9afb91baed93f2a026e",
      "question" : "introduce ",
      "trees" : {
        "0d98df8e7b8447f697b8d9da603055a1" : true
      }
    },
    "55431cf025ebe3f8bcf248d65ddb3442" : {
      "answer" : "58",
      "id" : "55431cf025ebe3f8bcf248d65ddb3442",
      "question" : "29+29",
      "trees" : {
        "664b7c53b3496bc44385db6a884bbe05" : true
      }
    },
    "55a811d27b392b0da11f360a6b3fa7cc" : {
      "answer" : "new answer",
      "id" : "55a811d27b392b0da11f360a6b3fa7cc",
      "question" : "new fact",
      "trees" : {
        "7fa13e85b721c0e4be28cb8ccab419be" : true
      }
    },
    "57b2624ee756cf5107e0742027186929" : {
      "answer" : "300",
      "id" : "57b2624ee756cf5107e0742027186929",
      "question" : "150+150",
      "trees" : {
        "ea328284bc8fbcb5ebaee8e5ee025995" : true
      }
    },
    "5833674b121a4bc28bdc9a3e4eede174" : {
      "answer" : ".",
      "id" : "5833674b121a4bc28bdc9a3e4eede174",
      "question" : "How to install grub on ubuntu"
    },
    "591fa736595d0f5c18c295a81046350b" : {
      "answer" : "it's who you know",
      "id" : "591fa736595d0f5c18c295a81046350b",
      "question" : "It's not what you know . . . "
    },
    "5a720e087aee4b08727dede1cc9d6ab0" : {
      "answer" : "96",
      "id" : "5a720e087aee4b08727dede1cc9d6ab0",
      "question" : "48+48",
      "trees" : {
        "c8085705f3d7809cb237969bc5413aa6" : true
      }
    },
    "5b798954b7c7414de1f232813e0ffb0b" : {
      "answer" : "flex-direction; justify-content; align-items; flex; flex-order; (Tip: direction, cross-axes, positioning, ordering)",
      "id" : "5b798954b7c7414de1f232813e0ffb0b",
      "question" : "List the 5 main flexbox properties:"
    },
    "5dbb7c2b00c6efb74e0a1ec2a2118ad8" : {
      "answer" : "48",
      "id" : "5dbb7c2b00c6efb74e0a1ec2a2118ad8",
      "question" : "24+24",
      "trees" : {
        "ae877fecbb2267e99f708f9db7eb79bc" : true
      }
    },
    "619a3ed7e1ca41843df5b38c4d886b2e" : {
      "answer" : "100",
      "id" : "619a3ed7e1ca41843df5b38c4d886b2e",
      "question" : "99+1"
    },
    "646d5d195d9f8ccc11546909c056b1fe" : {
      "answer" : "1100",
      "id" : "646d5d195d9f8ccc11546909c056b1fe",
      "question" : "100+1000",
      "trees" : {
        "adbb32059ed4ee5f81ea8f332745d374" : true
      }
    },
    "6508eb6337b05a4024d359648aaddd20" : {
      "answer" : "1801",
      "id" : "6508eb6337b05a4024d359648aaddd20",
      "question" : "ohio birth year",
      "trees" : {
        "0db75109953ce18e2b4cf22b71391c1a" : true
      }
    },
    "66bad44d508915e4e07f136ec57a728c" : {
      "answer" : "3000",
      "id" : "66bad44d508915e4e07f136ec57a728c",
      "question" : "1500+1500",
      "trees" : {
        "e307088f4cea4f2a0e71e3fd5e6ef3df" : true
      }
    },
    "67e03ab9c43fcda0de2faa1af3bad22b" : {
      "answer" : "180",
      "id" : "67e03ab9c43fcda0de2faa1af3bad22b",
      "question" : "90+90",
      "trees" : {
        "d733355e5b15f2835b5d3546300f7c9b" : true
      }
    },
    "6e882695fc07c0db7631dca9acd5e904" : {
      "answer" : "one222222",
      "id" : "6e882695fc07c0db7631dca9acd5e904",
      "question" : "another one"
    },
    "6e8c8f578b209d7b6c5e64f002358c5d" : {
      "answer" : "310",
      "id" : "6e8c8f578b209d7b6c5e64f002358c5d",
      "question" : "105+105",
      "trees" : {
        "868cd14dd9fd34c492af86278c9e45dd" : true
      }
    },
    "71a57f09fb8a449276423ae496d2e089" : {
      "answer" : "200",
      "id" : "71a57f09fb8a449276423ae496d2e089",
      "question" : "200",
      "trees" : {
        "69a2e17ef0017d6fa751a2f74cbeff4c" : true
      }
    },
    "76a4e2fec92008af6503342e8d9b4df2" : {
      "answer" : "42",
      "id" : "76a4e2fec92008af6503342e8d9b4df2",
      "question" : "21+21"
    },
    "78f67f0a87a781920dcbaf4e5609164f" : {
      "answer" : "2000",
      "id" : "78f67f0a87a781920dcbaf4e5609164f",
      "question" : "1000",
      "trees" : {
        "6c5deb8e17184af9e5f9a1bd7b77d0ef" : true
      }
    },
    "7db8cfdde0ea0b9864a9dce62eb460c1" : {
      "answer" : "41",
      "id" : "7db8cfdde0ea0b9864a9dce62eb460c1",
      "question" : "21+20"
    },
    "7f33fe2e758a34309321b339f8e24f7e" : {
      "answer" : "vauqery",
      "id" : "7f33fe2e758a34309321b339f8e24f7e",
      "question" : "al",
      "trees" : {
        "1745555255b5357e8cd2ad8368e129b4" : true
      }
    },
    "82290edac8f3196a1334439f82ebc35e" : {
      "answer" : "408",
      "id" : "82290edac8f3196a1334439f82ebc35e",
      "question" : "204",
      "trees" : {
        "071f15f1a74b6342ef3f2505c84eb206" : true
      }
    },
    "84b888fcf5171b9dca0e3ed169186f1f" : {
      "answer" : "255",
      "id" : "84b888fcf5171b9dca0e3ed169186f1f",
      "question" : "20"
    },
    "8564ecac0e2279bce855ad17cd52ad31" : {
      "answer" : "one333-999996666",
      "id" : "8564ecac0e2279bce855ad17cd52ad31",
      "question" : "another one225---999",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "88460995911b27c1d7b13c27950745f0" : {
      "answer" : "orangecakea",
      "id" : "88460995911b27c1d7b13c27950745f0",
      "question" : "apple",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "8a7889305c68d850ca57d78aeae2d94f" : {
      "answer" : "10000",
      "id" : "8a7889305c68d850ca57d78aeae2d94f",
      "question" : "1000",
      "trees" : {
        "80ae74cc975deebf71048bfb7eead187" : true
      }
    },
    "8c75afef296b8a448dc331a129f486dd" : {
      "answer" : "20",
      "id" : "8c75afef296b8a448dc331a129f486dd",
      "question" : "205"
    },
    "8e5b141b939db7c5d643c872d48d5172" : {
      "answer" : "70",
      "id" : "8e5b141b939db7c5d643c872d48d5172",
      "question" : "35+35",
      "trees" : {
        "726baf231297c759ddae8d05faaad6df" : true
      }
    },
    "8e820781516bbdab351424a5b209abbc" : {
      "answer" : "40",
      "id" : "8e820781516bbdab351424a5b209abbc",
      "question" : "20+20"
    },
    "8f0000b097e89decac858b5f447588ca" : {
      "answer" : "120",
      "id" : "8f0000b097e89decac858b5f447588ca",
      "question" : "60+60",
      "trees" : {
        "b5a4a2462edf3aaa2c6367f7eca61cce" : true
      }
    },
    "928db7705986c38e36aa3cb441cc7a28" : {
      "answer" : "0000",
      "id" : "928db7705986c38e36aa3cb441cc7a28",
      "question" : "2000"
    },
    "937bff00754ccca587b8eedd7303f902" : {
      "answer" : "wolrd",
      "id" : "937bff00754ccca587b8eedd7303f902",
      "question" : "hellow",
      "trees" : {
        "8b67fe6c491e3cacf69d5b032fde65be" : true
      }
    },
    "939f1e1a1067d8b58240a3aec1a3974e" : {
      "answer" : "b",
      "id" : "939f1e1a1067d8b58240a3aec1a3974e",
      "question" : "a"
    },
    "95aea60aed6781e6a81596f8c1a9632d" : {
      "answer" : "900",
      "id" : "95aea60aed6781e6a81596f8c1a9632d",
      "question" : "meth"
    },
    "9835ea744a11678ded120975364c08a3" : {
      "answer" : "2",
      "id" : "9835ea744a11678ded120975364c08a3",
      "question" : "5"
    },
    "98a4837433b2ec67a8b43592ba4d3c8e" : {
      "answer" : "220",
      "id" : "98a4837433b2ec67a8b43592ba4d3c8e",
      "question" : "20+200"
    },
    "99eac6bd8fc8cd450cf9a57c884d0987" : {
      "answer" : "090",
      "id" : "99eac6bd8fc8cd450cf9a57c884d0987",
      "question" : "909",
      "trees" : {
        "643ce56b033c66347ea744754d71d6de" : true
      }
    },
    "9b4554adbf2809787c32f6fed0c26241" : {
      "answer" : ".",
      "id" : "9b4554adbf2809787c32f6fed0c26241",
      "question" : "how to install grub on ubuntu"
    },
    "9b5c4a3fb1a4f239868fbd399ddecd83" : {
      "answer" : "21",
      "id" : "9b5c4a3fb1a4f239868fbd399ddecd83",
      "question" : "10+11"
    },
    "9d67c6c90e44c0e3737d65eeccb52534" : {
      "answer" : "4",
      "id" : "9d67c6c90e44c0e3737d65eeccb52534",
      "question" : "2+2",
      "trees" : {
        "11b079e2ac855ed39b32455238d75882" : true
      }
    },
    "a86074ee921271ee8961f410dc266096" : {
      "answer" : "yup",
      "id" : "a86074ee921271ee8961f410dc266096",
      "question" : "more facts",
      "trees" : {
        "9afb9c8278842fc6a54bc17146f86388" : true
      }
    },
    "aa42d09e11bd92f81c142dce3e21b24a" : {
      "answer" : "-3",
      "id" : "aa42d09e11bd92f81c142dce3e21b24a",
      "question" : "1-4"
    },
    "abdb7623bca3eca1918af5c1d76ed863" : {
      "answer" : "row; row-reverse; column; column-reverse",
      "id" : "abdb7623bca3eca1918af5c1d76ed863",
      "question" : "List the possible values for flex-direction"
    },
    "ad852f5df11cf523ea97ba5c1742a699" : {
      "answer" : "18",
      "id" : "ad852f5df11cf523ea97ba5c1742a699",
      "question" : "9+9",
      "trees" : {
        "8dea90e8f0ec59f44b23bb44cac289e9" : true
      }
    },
    "ad9f61ad865fc3864e7b7489789974f7" : {
      "answer" : "another a",
      "id" : "ad9f61ad865fc3864e7b7489789974f7",
      "question" : "another q",
      "trees" : {
        "339189bc37b5e8e3556837a4fdecd9ff" : true
      }
    },
    "affef7aabec1b8a4f590d19b8958a419" : {
      "answer" : "5000",
      "id" : "affef7aabec1b8a4f590d19b8958a419",
      "question" : "25",
      "trees" : {
        "7866f79ee5ffe01d8b2a7bb491cb21b2" : true
      }
    },
    "b2a10fd91d19bf3f64bb139e8d38ab75" : {
      "answer" : "2",
      "id" : "b2a10fd91d19bf3f64bb139e8d38ab75",
      "question" : "2"
    },
    "b884b6697f8b573f6185b98ccd66a64a" : {
      "answer" : "500",
      "id" : "b884b6697f8b573f6185b98ccd66a64a",
      "question" : "250",
      "trees" : {
        "c17a440f9ed65cf27e6b0eaddba4fa35" : true
      }
    },
    "bc62641cfd029c281b8ce6135d8991e0" : {
      "answer" : ". . . the more you earn",
      "id" : "bc62641cfd029c281b8ce6135d8991e0",
      "question" : "The more you learn . . . "
    },
    "bd5194d036858e1e4ad9a8b105fad087" : {
      "answer" : "one333-99999",
      "id" : "bd5194d036858e1e4ad9a8b105fad087",
      "question" : "another one225---999",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "be8912ae1ee0860769164465ca2b3819" : {
      "answer" : "one333-9999966667777",
      "id" : "be8912ae1ee0860769164465ca2b3819",
      "question" : "another one225---999",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "c0f938f7ec12403b023e66f7f1a7f9d4" : {
      "answer" : "one2222222",
      "id" : "c0f938f7ec12403b023e66f7f1a7f9d4",
      "question" : "another one",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "c1882855355c3e28c1389a1d8eb2a90a" : {
      "answer" : "44",
      "id" : "c1882855355c3e28c1389a1d8eb2a90a",
      "question" : "22+22"
    },
    "c4e82ce01bb89ae0835d808dda590e56" : {
      "answer" : "41",
      "id" : "c4e82ce01bb89ae0835d808dda590e56",
      "question" : "20+21"
    },
    "ca1581e0a032754cd442f788bb2a57d6" : {
      "answer" : "1776",
      "id" : "ca1581e0a032754cd442f788bb2a57d6",
      "question" : "When was America born",
      "trees" : {
        "0ff4568495c98e051aaa90c4c0e6ef75" : true
      }
    },
    "cb0bc7628803d376993530ca20cb8638" : {
      "answer" : "one",
      "id" : "cb0bc7628803d376993530ca20cb8638",
      "question" : "and yet another",
      "trees" : {
        "ab972bde40057cf68ed5f4ad1a312100" : true
      }
    },
    "cddefe9e59c864372d15f4a726bab2ee" : {
      "answer" : "250",
      "id" : "cddefe9e59c864372d15f4a726bab2ee",
      "question" : "new tree",
      "trees" : {
        "5312f6d44623aa6e8adf8a3d71e01915" : true
      }
    },
    "cf63d24a11b69f360a776dc6e37dce01" : {
      "answer" : "2200",
      "id" : "cf63d24a11b69f360a776dc6e37dce01",
      "question" : "2000+200",
      "trees" : {
        "dfdeadbbc3b821eaa4f34416ec0eefe0" : true
      }
    },
    "d084fc1aede3244d69da6c5d8cd564ec" : {
      "answer" : "89",
      "id" : "d084fc1aede3244d69da6c5d8cd564ec",
      "question" : "81+8",
      "trees" : {
        "284dd7ba0fe8acc92698ab15ea713e0b" : true
      }
    },
    "d1660a67b7c168bf465ead5a398fa7d3" : {
      "answer" : "52",
      "id" : "d1660a67b7c168bf465ead5a398fa7d3",
      "question" : "26+26",
      "trees" : {
        "63e52601788f87e335fb17cf66f69bf6" : true
      }
    },
    "d5a1ca0da9a23be18eed045d846faa95" : {
      "answer" : "444",
      "id" : "d5a1ca0da9a23be18eed045d846faa95",
      "question" : "44"
    },
    "d62e2f68e83093be7381ae0ff23464b6" : {
      "answer" : "2000",
      "id" : "d62e2f68e83093be7381ae0ff23464b6",
      "question" : "1000+1000",
      "trees" : {
        "78977c34024587e60d18d61737a5d07b" : true
      }
    },
    "d998259657a4a76791ec6713ab61e4dd" : {
      "answer" : "banana",
      "id" : "d998259657a4a76791ec6713ab61e4dd",
      "question" : "apple",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "dfc27295e2f5527812aad0539c68975b" : {
      "answer" : "20",
      "id" : "dfc27295e2f5527812aad0539c68975b",
      "question" : "10+10",
      "trees" : {
        "6f852491e942d616d3c0b2c87cef3c88" : true
      }
    },
    "e41b48edf89e0a90e2f9f3b4cf3a2c7b" : {
      "answer" : "79",
      "id" : "e41b48edf89e0a90e2f9f3b4cf3a2c7b",
      "question" : "2+77"
    },
    "e434b3adbce17ac765edcd61bb99541b" : {
      "answer" : "10",
      "id" : "e434b3adbce17ac765edcd61bb99541b",
      "question" : "5+5"
    },
    "e6f1c0faf53abebc3243d06f00ddcca1" : {
      "answer" : "one",
      "id" : "e6f1c0faf53abebc3243d06f00ddcca1",
      "question" : "and another ",
      "trees" : {
        "e58e8e42574499540e43b397cf17e52f" : true
      }
    },
    "e77f7232a6caa717d591fbe6bdd908c7" : {
      "answer" : "88",
      "id" : "e77f7232a6caa717d591fbe6bdd908c7",
      "question" : "80+8"
    },
    "ea5d7d8f8b3334489f618ad682677aed" : {
      "answer" : "167 hours",
      "id" : "ea5d7d8f8b3334489f618ad682677aed",
      "question" : "How Long does it take to learn spanish?"
    },
    "ecd1d2b273b3642feabbcc802d97bf0a" : {
      "answer" : "9",
      "id" : "ecd1d2b273b3642feabbcc802d97bf0a",
      "question" : "2+7"
    },
    "f19d0c829e21003524aad4306fa07ec4" : {
      "answer" : "one333",
      "id" : "f19d0c829e21003524aad4306fa07ec4",
      "question" : "another one225",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "f1d4e9e447a23219b18c821d501824f3" : {
      "answer" : "8",
      "id" : "f1d4e9e447a23219b18c821d501824f3",
      "question" : "2*4"
    },
    "f2d140f7e6675c6e5b214fa0a1a45f86" : {
      "answer" : "1807",
      "id" : "f2d140f7e6675c6e5b214fa0a1a45f86",
      "question" : "kentucky birthyear",
      "trees" : {
        "1d84092f684760a9b72f25f3cf2cd763" : true
      }
    },
    "f5c479743a5ffb284fb48c7dd39681b2" : {
      "answer" : "200?",
      "id" : "f5c479743a5ffb284fb48c7dd39681b2",
      "question" : "When was Europe Born",
      "trees" : {
        "89fb4eb795709b178a4951b0c6a4a96c" : true
      }
    },
    "f811596d26fdfbfa8f4bf196675025bc" : {
      "answer" : "one",
      "id" : "f811596d26fdfbfa8f4bf196675025bc",
      "question" : "another one",
      "trees" : {
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      }
    },
    "fe2dd8faf5555c8b51c6efbc9f1cad99" : {
      "answer" : "220",
      "id" : "fe2dd8faf5555c8b51c6efbc9f1cad99",
      "question" : "200+20"
    }
  },
  "trees" : {
    "1" : {
      "children" : {
        "5312f6d44623aa6e8adf8a3d71e01915" : true,
        "c17a440f9ed65cf27e6b0eaddba4fa35" : true,
        "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : true
      },
      "factId" : "24",
      "id" : 1,
      "treeId" : "1",
      "x" : -178.44976801222995,
      "y" : -93.53122549395698
    },
    "0d98df8e7b8447f697b8d9da603055a1" : {
      "factId" : "52128d0cb3c7d9afb91baed93f2a026e",
      "id" : "0d98df8e7b8447f697b8d9da603055a1",
      "parentId" : "c17a440f9ed65cf27e6b0eaddba4fa35",
      "x" : -113,
      "y" : 144
    },
    "0db75109953ce18e2b4cf22b71391c1a" : {
      "children" : {
        "1d84092f684760a9b72f25f3cf2cd763" : true
      },
      "factId" : "6508eb6337b05a4024d359648aaddd20",
      "id" : "0db75109953ce18e2b4cf22b71391c1a",
      "x" : -551.1551737019573,
      "y" : 31.994425507807648
    },
    "0ff4568495c98e051aaa90c4c0e6ef75" : {
      "factId" : "ca1581e0a032754cd442f788bb2a57d6",
      "id" : "0ff4568495c98e051aaa90c4c0e6ef75",
      "x" : -472.6048424008202,
      "y" : -55.509613759517485
    },
    "11b079e2ac855ed39b32455238d75882" : {
      "factId" : "9d67c6c90e44c0e3737d65eeccb52534",
      "id" : "11b079e2ac855ed39b32455238d75882",
      "parentId" : "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13",
      "x" : -551,
      "y" : 11.700838612248532
    },
    "1b4b4a8d797aa40d2b7d903cdbd8c3a9" : {
      "factId" : "1b15cf9a10eb0bec7262316d2bec6641",
      "id" : "1b4b4a8d797aa40d2b7d903cdbd8c3a9",
      "parentId" : "7fa13e85b721c0e4be28cb8ccab419be",
      "x" : -449,
      "y" : 15
    },
    "1d84092f684760a9b72f25f3cf2cd763" : {
      "factId" : "f2d140f7e6675c6e5b214fa0a1a45f86",
      "id" : "1d84092f684760a9b72f25f3cf2cd763",
      "parentId" : "0db75109953ce18e2b4cf22b71391c1a",
      "x" : -508,
      "y" : 48
    },
    "339189bc37b5e8e3556837a4fdecd9ff" : {
      "factId" : "ad9f61ad865fc3864e7b7489789974f7",
      "id" : "339189bc37b5e8e3556837a4fdecd9ff",
      "parentId" : "73ecf1917157fca001644715d88ae92c",
      "x" : -291,
      "y" : 104
    },
    "487f469c1ebb407cc4e9e378409c03ad" : {
      "factId" : "162307c8c731a2d855cc7e5d2d2ed5d8",
      "id" : "487f469c1ebb407cc4e9e378409c03ad",
      "parentId" : "9afb9c8278842fc6a54bc17146f86388",
      "x" : -367.7647378037399,
      "y" : 171.006200833229
    },
    "4b1878f15a03498637f6fa85aed40d7a" : {
      "children" : {
        "780df048605c9bf27ae84d859cc1fdeb" : true,
        "dfdeadbbc3b821eaa4f34416ec0eefe0" : true,
        "e307088f4cea4f2a0e71e3fd5e6ef3df" : true
      },
      "factId" : "438f6786355b28ea1887335fbde42750",
      "id" : "4b1878f15a03498637f6fa85aed40d7a",
      "x" : 13,
      "y" : 87
    },
    "5312f6d44623aa6e8adf8a3d71e01915" : {
      "factId" : "cddefe9e59c864372d15f4a726bab2ee",
      "id" : "5312f6d44623aa6e8adf8a3d71e01915",
      "parentId" : "1",
      "x" : -175,
      "y" : -18
    },
    "63e52601788f87e335fb17cf66f69bf6" : {
      "factId" : "d1660a67b7c168bf465ead5a398fa7d3",
      "id" : "63e52601788f87e335fb17cf66f69bf6",
      "parentId" : "c8085705f3d7809cb237969bc5413aa6",
      "x" : -252.26630016670617,
      "y" : 156.69050403423918
    },
    "664b7c53b3496bc44385db6a884bbe05" : {
      "factId" : "55431cf025ebe3f8bcf248d65ddb3442",
      "id" : "664b7c53b3496bc44385db6a884bbe05",
      "parentId" : "9dfb611221913a0393641eabd695af16",
      "x" : -156.7227039476564,
      "y" : 178
    },
    "69a2e17ef0017d6fa751a2f74cbeff4c" : {
      "factId" : "71a57f09fb8a449276423ae496d2e089",
      "id" : "69a2e17ef0017d6fa751a2f74cbeff4c",
      "parentId" : "b5a4a2462edf3aaa2c6367f7eca61cce",
      "x" : -272,
      "y" : 207
    },
    "69b8c8170d591d5721f5c3e1911963a1" : {
      "factId" : "2f2cd95f056dbaa163fe851a72de2645",
      "id" : "69b8c8170d591d5721f5c3e1911963a1",
      "parentId" : "e58e8e42574499540e43b397cf17e52f",
      "x" : -364,
      "y" : -44
    },
    "73ecf1917157fca001644715d88ae92c" : {
      "children" : {
        "339189bc37b5e8e3556837a4fdecd9ff" : true,
        "8b67fe6c491e3cacf69d5b032fde65be" : true
      },
      "factId" : "203f889239f025ab24d21adf750e21c7",
      "id" : "73ecf1917157fca001644715d88ae92c",
      "x" : -191,
      "y" : 4
    },
    "780df048605c9bf27ae84d859cc1fdeb" : {
      "children" : {
        "adbb32059ed4ee5f81ea8f332745d374" : true
      },
      "factId" : "0ae7c3ee894a117fe8f7f6dc2791c2aa",
      "id" : "780df048605c9bf27ae84d859cc1fdeb",
      "parentId" : "4b1878f15a03498637f6fa85aed40d7a",
      "x" : -206.42057871784573,
      "y" : 187
    },
    "7fa13e85b721c0e4be28cb8ccab419be" : {
      "children" : {
        "1b4b4a8d797aa40d2b7d903cdbd8c3a9" : true,
        "e5fe90c3606cbd0329d26e0f03c69812" : true
      },
      "factId" : "55a811d27b392b0da11f360a6b3fa7cc",
      "id" : "7fa13e85b721c0e4be28cb8ccab419be",
      "x" : -349.7638699126776,
      "y" : -85.7394733211529
    },
    "868cd14dd9fd34c492af86278c9e45dd" : {
      "factId" : "6e8c8f578b209d7b6c5e64f002358c5d",
      "id" : "868cd14dd9fd34c492af86278c9e45dd",
      "parentId" : "d733355e5b15f2835b5d3546300f7c9b",
      "x" : 165,
      "y" : 176
    },
    "89fb4eb795709b178a4951b0c6a4a96c" : {
      "factId" : "f5c479743a5ffb284fb48c7dd39681b2",
      "id" : "89fb4eb795709b178a4951b0c6a4a96c",
      "x" : -449.58147847204077,
      "y" : 6.734387253021524
    },
    "8b67fe6c491e3cacf69d5b032fde65be" : {
      "factId" : "937bff00754ccca587b8eedd7303f902",
      "id" : "8b67fe6c491e3cacf69d5b032fde65be",
      "parentId" : "73ecf1917157fca001644715d88ae92c",
      "x" : -73,
      "y" : 79
    },
    "967fd26e6fb4280f892e29bbd9d320cf" : {
      "factId" : "514bce83764babe8ad1a6775deaf7658",
      "id" : "967fd26e6fb4280f892e29bbd9d320cf",
      "parentId" : "ae877fecbb2267e99f708f9db7eb79bc",
      "x" : -397.92644973330357,
      "y" : 48.887551270774225
    },
    "9afb9c8278842fc6a54bc17146f86388" : {
      "children" : {
        "487f469c1ebb407cc4e9e378409c03ad" : true
      },
      "factId" : "a86074ee921271ee8961f410dc266096",
      "id" : "9afb9c8278842fc6a54bc17146f86388",
      "parentId" : "e5fe90c3606cbd0329d26e0f03c69812",
      "x" : -470,
      "y" : 94
    },
    "9dfb611221913a0393641eabd695af16" : {
      "children" : {
        "664b7c53b3496bc44385db6a884bbe05" : true,
        "ee9c8ef91bfac286cc285be1b2d608db" : true
      },
      "factId" : "0c7cc3c289412889547f299ee0707a02",
      "id" : "9dfb611221913a0393641eabd695af16",
      "parentId" : "c8085705f3d7809cb237969bc5413aa6",
      "x" : -115,
      "y" : 78
    },
    "ab972bde40057cf68ed5f4ad1a312100" : {
      "factId" : "cb0bc7628803d376993530ca20cb8638",
      "id" : "ab972bde40057cf68ed5f4ad1a312100",
      "parentId" : "e58e8e42574499540e43b397cf17e52f",
      "x" : -304,
      "y" : -25.31406744958298
    },
    "adbb32059ed4ee5f81ea8f332745d374" : {
      "factId" : "646d5d195d9f8ccc11546909c056b1fe",
      "id" : "adbb32059ed4ee5f81ea8f332745d374",
      "parentId" : "780df048605c9bf27ae84d859cc1fdeb",
      "x" : -187,
      "y" : 287
    },
    "ae877fecbb2267e99f708f9db7eb79bc" : {
      "children" : {
        "967fd26e6fb4280f892e29bbd9d320cf" : true,
        "ea328284bc8fbcb5ebaee8e5ee025995" : true
      },
      "factId" : "5dbb7c2b00c6efb74e0a1ec2a2118ad8",
      "id" : "ae877fecbb2267e99f708f9db7eb79bc",
      "x" : -185.42831034283645,
      "y" : 7
    },
    "b5a4a2462edf3aaa2c6367f7eca61cce" : {
      "children" : {
        "69a2e17ef0017d6fa751a2f74cbeff4c" : true,
        "d733355e5b15f2835b5d3546300f7c9b" : true
      },
      "factId" : "8f0000b097e89decac858b5f447588ca",
      "id" : "b5a4a2462edf3aaa2c6367f7eca61cce",
      "x" : -172.12592295915272,
      "y" : 107
    },
    "bba74ab62a49c87f65ff7c429f63ff92" : {
      "factId" : "0a01ba8c2b00e1e1ef3daea3580d351f",
      "id" : "bba74ab62a49c87f65ff7c429f63ff92",
      "x" : -417.51953596281396,
      "y" : 57.61900762918688
    },
    "c17a440f9ed65cf27e6b0eaddba4fa35" : {
      "children" : {
        "0d98df8e7b8447f697b8d9da603055a1" : true
      },
      "factId" : "b884b6697f8b573f6185b98ccd66a64a",
      "id" : "c17a440f9ed65cf27e6b0eaddba4fa35",
      "parentId" : "1",
      "x" : -237.66538899990826,
      "y" : 7
    },
    "c8085705f3d7809cb237969bc5413aa6" : {
      "children" : {
        "63e52601788f87e335fb17cf66f69bf6" : true,
        "9dfb611221913a0393641eabd695af16" : true
      },
      "factId" : "5a720e087aee4b08727dede1cc9d6ab0",
      "id" : "c8085705f3d7809cb237969bc5413aa6",
      "x" : -199,
      "y" : 6
    },
    "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13" : {
      "children" : {
        "11b079e2ac855ed39b32455238d75882" : true
      },
      "factId" : "341efa4830f32ad18815184b32b95117",
      "id" : "cb1f552dd507aef2cd335ca9fb941d13",
      "parentId" : "1",
      "x" : -488.2698311732971,
      "y" : -50.019514430438484
    },
    "d733355e5b15f2835b5d3546300f7c9b" : {
      "children" : {
        "868cd14dd9fd34c492af86278c9e45dd" : true
      },
      "factId" : "67e03ab9c43fcda0de2faa1af3bad22b",
      "id" : "d733355e5b15f2835b5d3546300f7c9b",
      "parentId" : "b5a4a2462edf3aaa2c6367f7eca61cce",
      "x" : 48.20321136479484,
      "y" : 141.0020587675045
    },
    "dfdeadbbc3b821eaa4f34416ec0eefe0" : {
      "factId" : "cf63d24a11b69f360a776dc6e37dce01",
      "id" : "dfdeadbbc3b821eaa4f34416ec0eefe0",
      "parentId" : "4b1878f15a03498637f6fa85aed40d7a",
      "x" : 22,
      "y" : 187
    },
    "e307088f4cea4f2a0e71e3fd5e6ef3df" : {
      "factId" : "66bad44d508915e4e07f136ec57a728c",
      "id" : "e307088f4cea4f2a0e71e3fd5e6ef3df",
      "parentId" : "4b1878f15a03498637f6fa85aed40d7a",
      "x" : -87,
      "y" : 187
    },
    "e58e8e42574499540e43b397cf17e52f" : {
      "children" : {
        "69b8c8170d591d5721f5c3e1911963a1" : true,
        "ab972bde40057cf68ed5f4ad1a312100" : true
      },
      "factId" : "e6f1c0faf53abebc3243d06f00ddcca1",
      "id" : "e58e8e42574499540e43b397cf17e52f",
      "x" : -260,
      "y" : -87.07768490172174
    },
    "e5fe90c3606cbd0329d26e0f03c69812" : {
      "children" : {
        "9afb9c8278842fc6a54bc17146f86388" : true
      },
      "factId" : "1d8c1d64bb06bb7046a238cd1b2bcfb3",
      "id" : "e5fe90c3606cbd0329d26e0f03c69812",
      "parentId" : "7fa13e85b721c0e4be28cb8ccab419be",
      "x" : -345.2076524381323,
      "y" : -6
    },
    "ea328284bc8fbcb5ebaee8e5ee025995" : {
      "factId" : "57b2624ee756cf5107e0742027186929",
      "id" : "ea328284bc8fbcb5ebaee8e5ee025995",
      "parentId" : "ae877fecbb2267e99f708f9db7eb79bc",
      "x" : -153.72048093727471,
      "y" : 107
    },
    "ee9c8ef91bfac286cc285be1b2d608db" : {
      "factId" : "2b70754fee385ef9eca7b02c9a8bbfd9",
      "id" : "ee9c8ef91bfac286cc285be1b2d608db",
      "parentId" : "9dfb611221913a0393641eabd695af16",
      "x" : -44.6955023972628,
      "y" : 169
    }
  }
}
